<odoo>

	<template id="report_purchase_order_custom">
		<t t-call="web.html_container">
			<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
				<t t-call="custom_po_report.external_layout_order">
					<t t-set="o" t-value="o.with_context(lang=lang)" />
					<div class="page">
					  	<div class="col-md-12">
		                    <table class="table table-bordered" style="padding: 0; margin: 0;">
								<tr>
									<th class="w-50 text-center">EXTERNAL PROVIDER DETAILS</th>
									<th class="w-50 text-center">DELIVERY ADDRESS</th>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>External Provider Number:</th>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>Name:</th>
									<td>Adams Advanced Aero Technology Company</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>Address:</th>
									<td>Khalid Branch Road, Khobar, PO Box 31952,<br/>Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>Contact:</th>
									<td>TEL: +966 13 802 1266 Fax (+966) (0) 13 802 0098</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>Email:</th>
									<td><a href="www.adamsaerotech.com">www.adamsaerotech.com</a></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>TEL:</th>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th>Vat no.</th>
									<td>VAT Reg: 3005114080003</td>
								</tr>
							</table>
							<br/>
							<table class="table table-bordered">
								<tr class="text-center">
									<td colspan="2"><strong>CONTROL</strong></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td class="w-25">Purchase Order Number /SR</td>
									<td><span>AAAT /00</span><span>/2021</span><span>Date:</span></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td class="w-25">Originating Requisition Number-</td>
									<td><span>AAAT /00</span><span>/2021</span><span>Date:</span></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Purchasing Department Contact</td>
									<td>DEEPAK SHETTY</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Telephone Number</td>
									<td>0097336111536</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Email</td>
									<td><a href="mailto:dshetty@adamsaerotech.com">dshetty@adamsaerotech.com</a></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Address</td>
									<td>Adams Advanced Aero Technology</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td></td>
									<td>Showroom No. 1, Plot No 55, Off King Khalid Branch Road</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td></td>
									<td>Khobar, PO Box 31962, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Contract Number</td>
									<td><span></span><span>Cost Centre Code No</span></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Shipping Method</td>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Terms of Payment</td>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Delivery Date</td>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Total Amount Payable</td>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Executive Approval</td>
									<td>MR. BILL HEDGES (Managing Director)</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Financial Approval </td>
									<td>Mr. IRSHAD NAZIMUDEEN (Finance Manager)</td>
								</tr>
							</table>
							<div>
								<p>This Purchase Order authorizes the supply of the items detailed below. Prices detailed below shall remain fixed until all the items requested in this Purchase Order have been supplied and delivered in good condition.</p>
								<p>Payment will be made upon provision and acceptance of the items detailed below unless alternative payments terms have been mutually agreed.</p>
								<p>All invoices must quote the correct Purchase Order Number and line-item numbers and should be sent to:</p>
								<p><i>Adams Advanced Aero Technology Company, Showroom No. 1, Plot No 55, Off King Khalid Branch Road Khobar 31952, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia. (AAAT Company cannot be held responsible for any delay in payment for any invoice incorrectly submitted).</i></p>
								<p class="mb-0">Alternatively, invoices may be emailed to</p>
								<p class="mb-0">For any queries relating to payment of invoices please call</p>
								<p class="mb-0">Phone <b>+966 13 802 1266</b> – Fax <b>+966 13 802 0098</b> or email <b><u>dshetty@adamsaerotech.com</u></b></p>
								<p class="mb-0"><b>Please refer to our full Terms and Conditions which are attached to this Purchase Order.</b></p>
							</div>
							<table class="table table-bordered">
								<tr>
									<th>Item No.</th>
									<th class="col-8">Description</th>
									<th>Quantity</th>
									<th>Unit Price</th>
									<th>Total Price</th>
								</tr>
								<tr t-foreach="o.order_line" t-as="line" class="text-center">
		                            <td><strong><t t-esc="line_index+1"/></strong></td>
		                            <td><t t-esc="line.product_id.name"/></td>
		                            <td><t t-esc="line.product_qty"/></td>
		                            <td><t t-esc="line.price_unit"/></td>
		                            <td><t t-esc="line.price_subtotal"/></td>
		                        </tr>
		                        <tr style="border:none;">
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;">Untaxed Amount</th>
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;"></th>
									<th class="text-end" style="border:1px solid #ddd;"><t  t-esc="o.amount_untaxed"/></th>
								</tr>
								<tr style="border:none;">
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;">Tax</th>
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;"></th>
									<th class="text-end" style="border:1px solid #ddd;"><t  t-esc="o.amount_tax"/></th>
								</tr>
								<tr style="border:none;">
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;">Total</th>
									<th colspan="2" class="text-end" style="border:none;"></th>
									<th class="text-end" style="border:1px solid #ddd;"><t  t-esc="o.amount_total"/></th>
								</tr>
							</table>
							<p><b>Acknowledgement of Order</b></p>
							<p>The supplier is requested to return, duly signed, the acknowledgement slip accompanying this Purchase Order within 7 days of the date of the order or as agreed in writing. Failure to do so will give the Purchaser the right to cancel the agreement within this Order, without incurring liability. The signature and return of the Order Acknowledgement Form shall constitute unconditional acceptance of the Order by the Supplier.</p>
							<p>Where the Supplier has not acknowledged the Order, and the Purchaser has not cancelled the Order, then commencement of the supply of goods mentioned in this Order shall deemed to be acknowledgement and unconditional acceptance of the Order by the Supplier.</p>
							<div class="row text-center">
								<h6 class="text-center">
									ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF PURCHASE ORDER
								</h6>
							</div>
							<table class="table table-bordered">
								<tr>
									<th class="col-3">Purchase Order Number</th>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th class="col-3">Date</th>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<th class="col-3">External Provider</th>
									<td></td>
								</tr>
							</table>
							<div class="py-5">
								<p>Please sign this Purchase Order Acknowledgement and return it to:<br/>…………………………………….</p>
								<p>
									Adams Advanced Aero Technology Company <br/>
									Showroom No. 1, Plot No 55, <br/>
									Off King Khalid Branch Road <br/>
									Khobar 31952, <br/>
									Kingdom Of Saudi Arabia <br/>
								</p>
								<p>Telephone: +966 13 802 0098 or +973 3611 1536</p>
								<p>Email: <a href="mailto:dshetty@adamsaerotech.com">dshetty@adamsaerotech.com</a></p>
								<p>This Acknowledgement should be signed and returned to the addressee within 7 days of the date shown above or within such period as may be agreed in writing. Failure to do so will give Adams Advanced Aero Technology Company the right to cancel this Purchase Order without incurring liability.</p>
							</div>
							<p class="py-5">Signed for and on behalf of :</p>
							<div class="mb-3">
								<span class="position-relative d-inline-block col-3 me-5">Signature:</span>
								<span>
								<input type="text" name="" style="border:none;border-bottom: 1px solid #aaa;width: 30%;"/>
								</span>
							</div>
							<div class="mb-3">
								<span class="position-relative d-inline-block col-3 me-5">Name:</span>
								<span>
								<input type="text" name="" style="border:none;border-bottom: 1px solid #aaa;width: 30%;"/>
								</span>
							</div>
							<div class="mb-3">
								<span class="position-relative d-inline-block col-3 me-5">Position”</span>
								<span>
								<input type="text" name="" style="border:none;border-bottom: 1px solid #aaa;width: 30%;"/>
								</span>
							</div>
							<br/>
							<div class="row text-center">
								<h6><strong>TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF PURCHASE</strong></h6>
							</div>
							<div>
								<p><b>1 Interpretation</b></p>
								<p>1.1 In these Conditions: "Conditions" means the standard terms and conditions of purchase set out in this document, and (unless the context otherwise requires) includes any special terms and conditions agreed in writing between the parties;</p>
								<p>"Contract" means the contract for the purchase of the Goods and/or the supply of the Services;</p>
								<p>"Customer" means the company named at the head of the Purchase Order;</p>
								<p>"Delivery Address" means the address stated on the Purchase Order;</p>
								<p>"Goods" means the goods (including any instalment of the goods or any part of them) described in the Purchase Order;</p>
								<p>"Price" means the price of the Goods and/or the charge for the Services;</p>
								<p>"Supplier" means the entity who is responsible for providing the Goods and/or the Services as stated in the Purchase Order; </p>
								<p>"Purchase Order" means the Customer's purchase order on the back of which are these Conditions, or in relation to an electronic purchase order, the Customer’s purchase order to which these Conditions are annexed;</p>
								<p>"Services" means the services (including any part of them) described in the Purchase Order;</p>
								<p>"Specification" includes any plans, drawings, data or other information relating to the Goods and/or the Services. </p>
								<p><b>2 Basis of Purchase </b></p>
								<p>2.1 This Purchase Order constitutes an offer by the Customer to purchase the Goods and/or the Services subject to these Conditions. Acceptance of this Purchase Order will bind the Supplier to these Conditions and no Goods and/or Services shall be supplied or performed by the Supplier, its employees, agents or representatives, except in accordance therewith</p>
								<p>2.2 These Conditions shall apply to the Contract to the exclusion of any other terms and conditions which the Supplier has sought to or may seek to impose on the Customer.</p>
								<p>2.3 No variation to the Purchase Order or these Conditions shall be binding unless agreed in writing between the authorised representatives of the parties.</p>
								<p><b>3 Specification </b></p>
								<p>3.1 The quantity, quality and description of the Goods and/or the Services shall, subject as provided in these Conditions, be specified in the Purchase Order and/or in any applicable Specification supplied by the Customer to the Supplier.</p>
								<p>3.2 The Supplier shall not unreasonably refuse any request by the Customer to inspect and test the Goods during manufacture, processing, or storage at the premises of the Supplier (or any third party) before dispatch, and the Supplier shall provide the Customer with all facilities reasonably required for inspection and testing.</p>
								<p>3.3 If as a result of inspection or testing carried out in accordance with Condition 3.3, the Customer is not satisfied that the Goods will comply in all respects with the Contract, the Supplier shall take such steps as are necessary to ensure compliance.</p>
								<p><b>4 Price and Payment</b></p>
								<p>4.1 The Price of the Goods and/or the Services shall be as stated in the Purchase Order and, unless stated otherwise, shall be inclusive of all charges for packaging, shipping, carriage, insurance and delivery of the Goods to the Delivery Address, and all duties or levies.</p>
								<p>4.2 No increase in the Price may be made (whether on account of increased material, labour or transport costs, fluctuation in rates of exchange or otherwise) without the prior consent of the Customer in writing.</p>
								<p>4.3 The Supplier's official invoice should be sent promptly to the Customer after delivery of the Goods and/or the Services, as the case may be, to the address indicated on front of the Purchase Order, unless otherwise instructed and must show:</p>
								<ul style="list-style: none;">
									<li>4.3.1 the Customer’s Purchase Order number;</li>
									<li>4.3.2 an Invoice number; </li>
									<li>4.3.3 a full description of the Good and/or the Works and/or the Services; </li>
									<li>4.3.4 full details of prices; and</li>
									<li>4.3.5 any discount allowed.</li>
								</ul>
							</div>
							<p>4.4 Unless otherwise stated in this Purchase Order or agreed in writing, the payment of the Price will be made within 30 days of receipt of a correct invoice, and upon the confirmation by an officer of the Customer that the Goods and/or the Services have been provided to the Customer’s satisfaction.</p>
							<p>4.5 The Customer shall be entitled to set-off against any invoice, any amount due from the Supplier under this Purchase Order or under any other contractual arrangement.</p>
							<p><b>5 Delivery</b></p>
							<p>5.1 The Goods shall be delivered to and/or the Services shall be performed at the Delivery Address on the date or within the period specified in the Purchase Order, in either case during the Customer's business hours.</p>
							<p>5.2 Where the date of delivery of the Goods and/or performance of the Services is to be specified after the placing of the Purchase Order, the Supplier shall give the Customer reasonable notice of the specified date.</p>
							<p>5.3 A delivery note which specifies the number of the Purchase Order shall accompany each delivery or consignment of the Goods, and must be displayed prominently.</p>
							<p>5.4 If the Goods are to be delivered and/or the Services are to be performed by instalments, the Contract will be treated as a single contract and will not be severable.</p>
							<p>5.5 The Customer shall be entitled to reject any Goods delivered which are not in accordance with the Contract, and shall not be deemed to have accepted any Goods until the Customer has had reasonable time to inspect them following delivery or, if later, within a reasonable time after any latent defect in the Goods has become apparent.</p>
							<p>5.6 The Supplier shall supply the Customer in good time with any instructions or other information required to enable the Customer to accept delivery of the Goods and/or performance of the Services.</p>
							<p>5.7 The Customer shall not be required to return to the Supplier any packaging or packaging materials for the Goods, whether or not the Goods are accepted by the Customer.</p>
							<p>5.8 If the Goods are not delivered and/or the Services are not performed on the due date then, without prejudice to any other remedy, the Customer shall be entitled to deduct from the Price or, if the Customer has already paid the Price, to claim from the Supplier an amount equal to the additional costs incurred by the Customer as a result of the delay.</p>
							<p>5.9 Risk of damage to or loss of the Goods shall pass to the Customer upon delivery to the Customer in accordance with the Contract.</p>
							<p>5.10 The property in the Goods shall pass to the Customer upon delivery, unless payment for the Goods i s made prior to delivery, where it shall pass to the Customer once payment has been made and the Goods have been appropriated to the Contract.</p>
							<p><b>6 Warranties and Liability</b></p>
							<p>6.1 The Supplier warrants to the Customer that the Goods will:</p>
							<ul style="list-style: none;">
								<li>6.1.1 be of sound materials and first class workmanship;</li>
								<li>6.1.2 be equal in all respects to the samples, patterns, description or specification provided or given by either party; </li>
								<li>6.1.3 if the purpose for which they are required is indicated, either expressly or by implication, in the Purchase Order or otherwise be fit for that purpose and;</li>
								<li>
									<ul style="list-style: none;">
										<li>6.1.3.1 be of satisfactory quality; </li>
										<li>6.1.3.2 be free from defects in design, material and workmanship; and</li>
										<li>6.1.3.3 will comply with all local requirements and regulations relating to the sale of the Goods. </li>
									</ul>
								</li>
							</ul>
							<p>6.2 The Supplier warrants to the Customer that the Services will be performed by appropriately trained and qualified personnel, with due care and diligence, and to the standards which would reasonably be expected from a skilled and experienced provider engaged in the provision of services similar to the Services under the same or similar circumstances.</p>
							<p>6.3 The Supplier will indemnify the Customer in full against the following:</p>
							<ul style="list-style: none;">
								<li>6.3.1 all loss, liability, damages, costs, expenses (including legal expenses) or injury whatsoever and whenever arising caused to the Customer, or for which the Customer may be liable to third parties due to defective workmanship or unsound quality of the Goods and/or the Services supplied;</li>
								<li>6.3.2 all claims in respect of death or injury, howsoever caused, to any of the employees, or those of the agent or subcontractors, of the Supplier, while in or about the Customer’s sites, works or othe r places of business;</li>
							</ul>
							<ul style="list-style: none;">
								<li>6.3.3 any consequential loss or damage sustained by the Customer for which the Customer may be liable, as a result of the failure of the Supplier to supply the materials or perform the work in accordance with the terms of this Purchase Order.</li>
							</ul>
							<p>6.4 The Supplier having given the above indemnity shall maintain in force during the term of the Contract full and comprehensive insurance as appropriate in respect of the provision of the Goods and/or Services such insurance to be with reputable insurers acceptable to the Customer acting reasonably</p>
							<p>6.5 Without prejudice to any other remedy, if any of the Goods and/or Services are not supplied or performed in accordance with the Contract, then the Buyer shall be entitled:</p>
							<ul style="list-style: none;">
								<li>6.5.1 to require the Supplier to repair the Goods or to supply replacement Goods and/or Services in compliance with the Contract within 7 days; or</li>
								<li>6.5.2 at the Customer’s sole option and whether or not the Customer has previously required the Supplier to repair the Goods or to supply any replacement Goods and/or Services, to treat the Contract as discharged by the Supplier’s breach and require repayment of any part of the Price which has been paid.</li>
							</ul>
							<p><b>7 Termination</b></p>
							<p>7.1 The Customer shall be entitled to cancel the Contract in respect of all or part only of the Goods and/or the Services by giving notice to the Supplier at any time prior to delivery or performance, in which event the Customer's sole liability shall be to pay the Supplier the Price for the Goods and/or the Services in respect of which the Customer has exercised it rights of cancellation, less the Supplier's net saving of cost arising from the cancellation.</p>
							<p>7.2 The Customer shall be entitled to terminate the Contract without liability to the Supplier by giving notice to the Supplier at any time if: </p>
							<ul style="list-style: none;">
								<li>7.2.1 the Supplier becomes bankrupt or becomes subject to an administration order or goes into liquidation (otherwise than for the purpose of amalgamation or reconstruction) or otherwise ceases, or threatens to cease to carry on business; or</li>
								<li>7.2.2 the Supplier does anything improper to influence the Customer to give the Supplier any contract; or</li>
								<li>7.2.3 the Customer reasonably believes that any of the events mentioned above is about to occur in relation to Supplier and notifies the Supplier</li>
							</ul>
							<p>7.3 For the avoidance of doubt, where the Customer terminates the Contract in accordance with the provisions of Condition 8.2, the Supplier shall compensate the Customer for any losses suffered as a result of this. </p>
							<p><b>8 General</b></p>
							<p>8.1 The Supplier not transfer, assign or sub-let, directly or indirectly, to any person whatever, the whole or any portion of this Contract without the written permission of the Customer.</p>
							<p>8.2 Any notice required or permitted to be given by either party to the other party under these Conditions shall be in writing addressed to that other party. </p>
							<p>8.3 No waiver by the Customer of any breach of the Contract by the Supplier shall be considered as a waiver of any subsequent breach of the same or any other provision.</p>
							<p>8.4 These Conditions and the Purchase Order constitute the entire understanding between the parties relating to the subject matter of the Contract and, save as may be expressly referred to or referenced herein, supersede all prior representations, writings, negotiations or understandings with respect hereto, except in respect of any fraudulent misrepresentation made by either party.</p>
							<p>8.5 Save for the Parties, no person shall have any right to enforce any of the terms of this Purchase Order and/or these Conditions.</p>
		                </div>
					</div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</t>
	</template>
	<record id="purchase_order_custom" model="ir.actions.report">
        <field name="name">Adams Purchase Order</field>
        <field name="model">purchase.order</field>
        <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
        <field name="report_name">custom_po_report.report_purchase_order_custom</field>
        <field name="report_file">custom_po_report.report_purchase_order_custom</field>
        <field name="binding_model_id" ref="purchase.model_purchase_order"/>
        <field name="binding_type">report</field>
    </record>
</odoo>